rupikahanumantu@gmail.com

RUPIKA HANUMANTU 8639797689

Assistant Operations Manager

Gajuwaka, Visakhapatnam, India

LinkedIn: Rupika Hanumantu

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Motivated professional with up to 2 years of experience in banking sector. Specialized in client on boarding and client management. Experienced in monitoring complex account activities. Strong relationship management skills.

Highly adept at comprehensive Finacle Operations, Transaction Monitoring, Investment Banking, Branch Management, Business Development, Profit Centre Operations, Retail Banking, and Team Management.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

KOTAK MAHINDRA BANK, Visakhapatnam

Assistant Manager in operations

Experience: July 2022 to Till Date Process: Branch banking operations

Role : Assistant Manager in Operations

- Handling branch banking operations using Finacle application and doing tax payments through Ultra GBM and GBM applications.
- As an Assistant manager increased portfolio growth and used to manage Client meetings and calls through CRM actioning.
- Maintaining and managing existing accounts to ensure business sustainability.
- Proficient in implementing strategies towards enhancing business volumes and growth.
- Expertise in ensuring compliance to bank guidelines and implementing control systems to reduce the risk of loss and reputational damage to the bank.

ICICI Bank Ltd., Visakhapatnam

Relationship Manager

Experience: May 2021 to June 2022

Process: Banking Operations and Gold loan Operations

Role : Senior Officer

- Handled core branch banking operations and Gold loan Operations Using Finacle (I-core) and i-gold applications.
- Implemented competent strategies with a view to penetrate new accounts and expand existing ones for a wide range of banking products / services.
- Attended investors / clients (individuals / corporate clients) concerns and undertaking steps for resolving them.
- Ensured compliance of various statutory requirements as per audit guidelines as well as regulations laid down by various acts governing banking operations.
- Addressed all aspects of risks including credit, market and operational risks.
- Worked on various credit operations involving appraising proposals and scrutinized relevant documents before sanctioning loans.

EDUCATION

B.Tech

University of Petroleum and Energy Studies (UPES)

April 2014 – April 2018

(Dehradun) *Uttarakhand*

 ${\bf Computer\ Science\ with\ \it SPECIALIZATION-E-Commerce\ and\ Retail\ Automation}$